Willard Thorp and Margaret Farrand Thorp Papers, 1886-1981 (bulk 1930-1970): Finding Aid C0292
Manuscripts Division
Willard Thorp and Margaret Farrand Thorp Papers
1886-1981
1930-1970
Manuscripts Division
Princeton University. Library. Special Collections
Thorp, Margaret Farrand, 1891-1970
Thorp, Willard, 1899-1990
C0292
33 boxes
14.1 linear feet
Consists of material which reflects the long careers of American educators, authors, and literary critics Willard and Margaret Thorp. Willard's papers (1923-1981) include correspondence, writings, class lecture notes, documents, journals and diaries, printed matter, photographs, and papers of others during his writing and teaching years at Princeton University. Margaret's papers (1917-1960) include writings, correspondence, journals, notebooks, and family sketchbooks and photographs.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of papers reflective of both Willard and Margaret Thorp's careers as authors and critics, Willard's years as a professor of English at Princeton University, and Margaret's early career in journalism. The bulk of the collection dates from the years (1930-1970) when they published the majority of their articles, reviews and books, gave their speeches, and when Willard taught his classes and was acting chairman of Princeton's English Department.
Willard's papers consist mainly of correspondence with professional colleagues; friends, particularly Allen Tate and Caroline Gordon, but also including T. S. Eliot, William Meredith, James Meriwether, Robert Penn Warren, Robert Lowell, Archibald MacLiesh, and John Berryman; organizations, such as the Modern Language Association, and the Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni; and publishers of his works, including the American Book Company, Charles Scribner's Sons, and the J. B. Lippincott Company. Much of the correspondence relates to books he wrote or contributed to, such as Modern Writing, The Lives of Eighteen from Princeton, Great Short Works of American Realism, and A Southern Reader. There are also manuscripts of articles and speeches Willard wrote, as well as class lecture notes of the courses he taught at Princeton (1932-1967), miscellaneous material regarding a senior poetry seminar, several diaries, publisher's contracts, photographs, printed matter, papers of others, and four recording of conversations with Thorp. Included is an album of original poems dedicated to Willard by seven Princeton poets, presumably his former students. A later accession consists of over 100 offprints of articles by contemporary literary scholars and critics; many of these pamphlets are inscribed to Thorp.
Margaret's papers consist of drafts of Charles Kingsley, 1819-1875 and Female Persuasion: Six Strong-Minded Women, speeches, articles, notebooks, correspondence with Allen Tate and Caroline Gordon, Vivienne Heigh (Mrs. T. S. Eliot), family letters and correspondence with her publishers, and family sketchbooks and photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Willard and Margaret Thorp both donated their works to Princeton University in installments over the years 1948-1989; when Margaret died in 1970, Willard donated her work as well as his own. A small amount of material in Willard's correspondence and documents sections are photostats (the location of the originals is unknown) and, for preservation purposes, some old newspaper clippings have been Xeroxed and the originals destroyed.
Appraisal
No appraisal information is available.
Thorp, Margaret Farrand, 1891-1970
Biographical / Historical
Margaret Louise Farrand Thorp (1891-1970), scholar, author, critic, and journalist, was born in East Orange, New Jersey, on December 3, 1891. She graduated from Smith College in 1914, received her M.A. from Smith in 1926, and her Ph.D. from Yale in 1934.
After receiving her B.A., Margaret worked on the staff of The Independent under the editorship of Hamilton Holt. A firm believer in the cause of the Allies, she was eager to get to France to serve in any way she could. The American Fund for French Wounded accepted her, and in late October 1917 she sailed for France on the Rochambeau. Once there, she edited The Weekly Bulletin issued by the Fund Cooperating with the American Red Cross for circulation in the United States. (Alice B. Toklas was one of its frequent contributors.) In her spare time Margaret worked in the canteens and as an unofficial nurse's aide in several hospitals. In March 1918 she transferred to the American Red Cross where she continued to do publicity work until after the Armistice. She was also a special correspondent to the Newark Evening Times and wrote faithfully in her own journals, recording all her experiences.
After returning from France, between 1921 and 1929, Margaret was Director of Publicity and Assistant Professor of English at Smith College. Also during this time she was a regular contributor to such publications as The Smith Alumnae Quarterly, the Christian Science Monitor, Scribner's Magazine, and the New York Evening Post. In 1929 she went to Yale to earn her Ph.D., and on June 12 of the following year married Willard Thorp, then an assistant professor at Princeton University.
Although Margaret did not continue teaching after her marriage, she continued to pursue her writing career. In 1937 she published Charles Kingsley, 1819-1875 with Princeton University Press. In 1969 Yale University Press published her popular film study, America at the Movies. In 1944 she collaborated with Willard on a textbook, Modern Writing, followed by another biography, Female Persuasion: Six Strong-Minded Women in 1949. Later writings include Neilson of Smith (1956), The Literary Sculptors (1965), and Sara Orne Jewett (1966).
In 1957 Smith College made Margaret Thorp an honorary Doctor of Letters. She died in Princeton on October 2, 1970, at the age of 79. She was a niece of Beatrix Farrand, Princeton's landscape artist.
Thorp, Willard, 1899-1990
Biographical / Historical
William Willard Thorp (1899-1990), literary historian, editor, educator, author, and critic, was born on April 20 in Sydney, New York. He graduated Phi Beta Kappa from Hamilton College in 1920, received an A.M. the following year from Harvard, and his Ph.D. in 1926 from Princeton University. That year he joined the faculty of Princeton and advanced from instructor of English in 1926 to the Holmes Professor of Belles Lettres in 1952, and was chairman of the English department from 1958-1963.
During his years at Princeton, Willard Thorp published a number of books, innumerable literary reviews and essays in philogical journals, and established himself as an editor. Included among his books are The Triumph of Realism in Elizabethan Drama (1928), Lives of Eighteen from Princeton (1946), A Southern Reader (1955), and American Writing in the 20th Century (1960). One of his best-known essays is "The Well of English, Now Defiled, or, Why Johnny Can't Write," a humorous piece with serious undertones in which Thorp laments the state of affairs of college writing. He edited with Howard Lowry the Oxford Anthology of English Poetry (Oxford University Press, 1935), and with various others edited Herman Melville, Representative Selections (American Book Company, 1938), and the widely-used Herman Melville, Moby-Dick (Oxford University Press, 1948), Literary History of the United States (first published in 1948), and Great Short Works of American Realism (Harper, 1968).
Aside from his literary accomplishments and his popularity with undergraduates, one of Willard Thorp's greatest contributions to Princeton University was the development in 1942 of the special program in American civilization, now called the American Studies Program. He directed this for the first thirteen years, and strove to bring American civilization to light through studying culture, institution, intellectual tradition, and relationships among groups. The program grew until it included faculty and undergraduates from nine cooperating departments. One of the special interest courses taught by Thorp in this program was "The Age of Dryden."
Willard Thorp also kept busy traveling to various universities as a visiting professor. He went to the University of Virginia in 1947, was the Anderson Visiting Professor at the Rice Institute in 1952-1953, and taught summers at the University of Hawaii, University of Washington, Seattle, and Duke University.
Thorp retired from Princeton University in 1967, remaining in Princeton until his death at age 90 in 1990. He was honored in 1972 with the establishment of the Willard Thorp Thesis Prize in American Civilization, and in 1978 was awarded an L.H.D.
1899 Born in Sidney, New York, on April 20
1920 A.B., Hamilton College
1921 A.M., Harvard University
1921-1924 instructor, then became assistant professor, Smith College
1926 Ph.D., Princeton University
1926-1928 instructor in English, Princeton University
1928 published The Triumph of Realism in Elizabethan Drama, Princeton University Press
1928-1939 assistant professor, Princeton University
1930 married Margaret Farrand on June 12
1931-1932 Fellow, American Council of Learned Societies
1932 published Poetry of the Transition, 1850-1914 with Thomas M. Parrott, Oxford University Press
1934 published Songs from the Restoration Theater, Princeton University Press
1935 published Oxford Anthology of English Poetry with Howard Lowry, Oxford University Press
1936 summer professor, University of Hawaii
1938 published Herman Melville, Representative Selections, American Book Company
1939-1944 associate professor, Princeton University
1944 published Modern Writing with Margaret Farrand Thorp, American Book Company
1944 professor, Princeton University
1944-1949 Fellow of American Letters, Library of Congress
1946 published Lives of Eighteen from Princeton, Princeton University Press
1947 Honorary Litt. D. from Hamilton College
1948 published Herman Melville, Moby-Dick, Oxford University Press
1950-1957 member of the editorial board, American Literature
1952 Holmes Professor of Belles Lettres, Princeton University
1952-1953 Anderson Visiting Professor, Rice Institute, Texas
1954-1957 executive council, Modern Language Association
1955 published A Southern Reader, Alfred A. Knopf
1958-1959 president, American Studies Association
1958-1963 chairman, Department of English, Princeton University
1960 published American Writing in the Twentieth Century, Harvard University Press
1960 L.H.D. from Kalamazoo College
1966-1967 Guggenheim fellow
1967 retired from Princeton University
1968 published Great Short Works of the American Renaissance, Harper
1968 published Great Short Works of American Realism, Harper
1990 died in Princeton, February 15, at 90 years old
American poetry -- 20th century.; American poetry -- Study and teaching -- New Jersey -- Princeton -- 20th century.; Authors and publishers -- United States -- 20th century -- Correspondence.; Critics -- United States -- Correspondence.; Women authors, American--20th century.; Women in journalism—United States—History—20th century.; Women journalists—United States.; American diaries -- 20th century.; Correspondence.; Notebooks.; Photographs.; Modern language association of America; Gordon, Caroline, 1895-1981; Tate, Allen, 1899-1979
- Series 1: Papers of Willard Thorp, 1916-1986; 23 boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Collection is open for research use.
  Scope and Contents
  Consists of the papers pf Willard Thorp, including correspondence, writings, journals, address books, documents, photographs, and recordings.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged into eight subseries: Correspondence, Writings, Journals and Address Book, Documents (Awards, Certificates, Contracts, Genealogies, Etc.), Photographs, Printed Matter, Papers of Others, and Recordings.
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence, 1926-1986; 12 boxes
    The majority of Willard Thorp's material consists of general correspondence and correspondence related to his writings (fan mail, publication, etc.). A small amount of family letters begins the section, followed by the correspondence reflecting his long-standing friendships and working relationships with Allen Tate, James Meriwether, William Meredith, Robert Lowell, T.S. Eliot, Bink Noll, Galway Kinnell, John Berryman, Louis Coxe, Archibald MacLiesh, Robert Penn Warren, Carl Sandburg, and Elizabeth Bishop. He also corresponded with a host of students and colleagues, including Jesse Bier, Andrew Hook, Sam Monk, Jim Kempf, and James Brogan, on both personal and business levels. There is correspondence regarding his books, including A Southern Reader (1955), the Oxford Anthology of English Poetry (1935), Moby Dick (1948), and Thorp's other Melville works, and two works of which Willard wrote the introductory paragraph: Great Short Works of American Realism (1968) and Henry David Thoreau's Walden. There is correspondence regarding his honorary degree at the June 6, 1978, Princeton University commencement, his term on the Phi Beta Kappa Nominating Committee (1949-1957), the Higher Learning in the United States Conference at Princeton's graduate college (June 14-18, 1956), the Sixteenth Annual Faculty-Alumni Forum Program (June 8, 1967) (Willard served as moderator), and the Modern Language Association of American (executive council, 1954-1957); correspondence with publishers, such as Signet Classics, American Book Company, and Alfred A. Knopf (with whom Willard corresponded personally); recommendations of students and colleagues; and notes of a senior seminar.
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - Family Letters, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - A (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alfred A. Knopf, 1952-1955; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Book Company, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American H-Arr, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - American Issues to The American Literary Record (revision) correspondence, 1954-1961; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The American Studies Association (ASA), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Arvin, Newton, 1938-1948; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Asb-Assel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - The Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Ast-Au, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - B-Bar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Beard, James, 1964-1976; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bed-Ber, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bezanson, Walter, 1951-1969; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Biddle, Katherine, 1946-1963; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Biddle, Livingston, 1943-1963; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bie-Ble, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Blo-Bowe, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Blickensderfer, Joseph P.: The United States Quarterly Book List, 1944-1956; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bowman, Heath, 1931-1976; 1 box
      - 1931-1936, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 1937-1944, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - 1945-1976, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Boy-Bre, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Brice, Ashbel, 1971-1975; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Briggs, Grace, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Broderick, Francis L. (Frank), 1943-1968; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Brogan, Jim, 1965-1971; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Broo-Bru, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bu-But, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - C (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Cartwright, Levering, 1966-1981; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Cas-Chapl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Chapman, Robert, 1942-1965; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Chas-Cow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1944-1985; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Coxe, Louis O., 1942-1985; 1 box
      - 1942-1955, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - 1956-1969, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - and Robert, 1970-1985; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cra-Cre, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Crimmins, Thomas, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cro-D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - E-Eg, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Eight American Authors correspondence, 1954-1956; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Eliot, Thomas Stearns, 1931-1960; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Eliot, Thomas Stearns, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Els-Fr, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Fox, Frederick, 1964 March 16-17; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 5a)
    - "Fugitives Reunion", Nashville, TN, 1956 May 3-5; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "Fugitives Reunion", Nashville, TN, Group Photograph, 1956 May 3-5; 1 box (Box 33)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      AM 87-61
      Includes identifying information of those in the photo.
    - Fur-Garr, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Gary, Franklin, 1963-1977; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Ge-Gra, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Great Short Works of American Realism: introduction by Willard Thorp, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Gree-Gw, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - H-Hac, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Hale, Emily, 1956-1967; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Ham-Haw, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Hayford, Harrison, 1952-1970; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hayw-Hell, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Hendricks, Walter, 1946-1957; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Henn-High, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Higher Learning in the United States Conference: Princeton University Graduate College, 1956 June 14-18; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hil-Hin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Holland, Laurence B, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Holm-Holv, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Honorary Degree: Princeton University Commencement, 1978 June 6; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Hook, Andrew, 1962-1976; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Hop-Hors, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Horton, Phillip, 1931-1950; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Hos-K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Kempf, Jim, 1967-1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Ken-Kr, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - La Fay, Howard, 1944-1950; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Lac-Lew, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Lil-Lip, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - The Lives of Eighteen from Princeton correspondence, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Library of Congress Fellows in American Letters, 1944-1951; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Lo-Mack, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - MacLiesh, Archibald, 1937-1962; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - MacN-Martin, Bob, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Martin, Jay, 1962-1970; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Mas-McD, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - McElroy, John, 1967-1973; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - McElv-Mee, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Melville, Herman: correspondence relating to works, 1935-1959; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Meredith, William, 1940-1981; 1 box
      - 1940-1944, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 1945-1968, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - 1969-1981, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Meriwether, Jim, 1958-1983; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mes-Mi, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Moby Dick correspondence before publication (Oxford University Press), 1941-1947; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Moby Dick correspondence after publication (Oxford University Press), 1946-1951; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Modern Language Association of America (MLAA), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Modern Language Association of America (MLAA) Executive Council, 1954-1957; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Monk, Sam, 1931-1981; 2 boxes
      - 1931-1947, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - 1948-1970, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - 1971-1981, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - undated, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Monro-Ni, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Noll, Bink, 1950-1986; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Nor-Os, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - An Oxford Anthology of English Poetry correspondence, 1950-1956; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - P-Pe, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Phi Beta Kappa National Nominating Committee, 1949-1957; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Pi-Princeton P, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Princeton University, 1926-1984; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Princeton University Press-Rea, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Rei-Rub, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Ruckeyser, Muriel, 1940-1956; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Rudd, Bob, 1958; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Rushton lectures-Birmingham-Southern College, 1956 November; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Rushton, Pete, 1942-1947; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Rut-Sal, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Sandburg, Carl, 1950-1959; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sav-See, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Senior Seminar, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Seymour, Sy L, 1941; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Shain, Charles, 1946-1976; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Shaine, F. M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Shapiro, Karl, 1946-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - She-Shu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Signet Classics correspondence, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Sim-Sin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sixteenth Annual Faculty-Alumni Forum Program, 1967 June 8; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
      (Thorp's notes for remarks as moderator)
    - Sk-Soc, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - A Southern Reader correspondence, 1949-1952; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - A Southern Reader correspondence with Thomas Bledsoe, Alfred A. Knopf Publishers, 1954-1955; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - A Southern Reader reviews, notices, and correspondence, 1953-1956; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Sp, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Stegner, Wallace, 1941-1945; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Stev-Stone, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Stovall, Floyd, 1951-1974; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Str-Stub, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stutesman, John, 1944-1948; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Sue-Taf, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Tate, Allen, 1939-1974; 2 boxes
      - 1939-1949, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1950-1955, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - 1956-1970, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - 1971-1974, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Tay-Thom, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Thoreau, Henry David: Walden-correspondence relating to introduction by Willard Thorp, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Thorp, Christina, 1960-1984; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Thorp, J-U, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)